Old Coast, Australia

**** 0490 782 726

Profile

26 years old Italian Bartender with extraordinary customer service skills and a motivated attitude. Knowledgeable about drink combinations, free-pouring techniques, and flair bartending moves. Adept at maintaining a clean and organized bar area, practicing the Clean-As-You-Go policy.

Employment History

Lifeguard, Islamorada Dog Beach, Fano (Italy)

May 2014 — September 2016

Worked for three summer seasons (2014/15/16)

- Utilized excellent surveillance skills.
- Remained flexible, adaptable and punctual.
- Occasionally worked as a bartender during night events.

Bartender, Circolo ARCI, Corinaldo (Italy)

September 2016 — January 2017

- Greeted guests with a friendly and helpful attitude at all times.
- Carried on friendly conversations with patrons and answered any questions or concerns to the best of my ability.
- Followed directions and took initiative when appropriate.

Fruit Picker, Australia

February 2017 — September 2022

Bartender and Barista, Garagol Beach, Fano (Italy)

May 2018 — September 2018

- Waited at tables, taking drink orders in this high-traffic bar.
- Utilized excellent public speaking skills.
- Brought forth a positive and self-motivated attitude.
- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- Provided guests with drink suggestions and knowledge about drink recipes.

Education

I.I.S. Volterra-Elia, Ancona (Italy)

September 2010 — June 2016

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Degree at the Industrial Technical Institute Volterra-Elia

European Bartender School, Milan

February 2018 — April 2018

Certificate IV in Business, Greystone College, Brisbane

August 2020 — May 2021

Links

Facebook

Instagram

LinkedIn

Personal Website (under construction)

Skills

Customer Service

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Computer Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Analytical Thinking

Languages

Italian

English

Spanish; Castilian

Hobbies

Football, Videogames, Cocktails & Poker